<doc>
	<entry path="/Maps">Represents a Map to be created inside of the div element.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/height">The height of the Map's div container.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/width">The width of the Map's div container.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/ondragend">This event is fired when the user stops dragging the Map.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/onmaptypeid_changed">This event is fired when the mapTypeId property changes.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/ontilt_changed">This event is fired when the Map tilt property changes.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/onzoom_changed">This event is fired when the Map zoom property changes.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/onheading_changed">This event is fired when the map heading property changes.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options">Options for customizing the Map.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/backgroundcolor">Color used for the background of the Map div.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/disabledefaultui">Enables/disables all default UI.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/disabledoubleclickzoom">Enables/disables zoom and center on double click.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/draggable">If false, prevents the map from being dragged.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/draggablecursor">The name or url of the cursor to display on a draggable object.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/draggingcursor">The name or url of the cursor to display when an object is dragging.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/maptypecontrol">The initial enabled/disabled state of the Map type control.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/keyboardshortcuts">If false, prevents the map from being controlled by the keyboard.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/maxzoom">The maximum zoom level which will be displayed on the map.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/minzoom">The minimum zoom level which will be displayed on the map.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/noclear">If true, do not clear the contents of the Map div.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/overviewmapcontrol">The enabled/disabled state of the Overview Map control.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/pancontrol">The enabled/disabled state of the Pan control.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/rotatecontrol">The enabled/disabled state of the Rotate control.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/scalecontrol">The initial enabled/disabled state of the Scale control.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/scrollwheel">If false, disables scrollwheel zooming on the map. </entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/streetviewcontrol">The initial enabled/disabled state of the Street View Pegman control. This control is part of the default UI, and should be set to false when displaying a map type on which the Street View road overlay should not appear (e.g. a non-Earth map type).</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/zoomcontrol">The enabled/disabled state of the Zoom control.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/zoom">The initial Map zoom level. Required.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/maptypeid">The initial Map mapTypeId. Required.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/center">The initial Map center. Required.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/center/direct">Direct lat/lng specification of the Map center.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/center/direct/latitude">Latitude in degrees.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/center/direct/longitude">Longitude in degrees.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/center/direct/nowrap">If the noWrap flag is true, then the numbers will be used as passed, otherwise latitude will be clamped to lie between -90 degrees and +90 degrees, and longitude will be wrapped to lie between -180 degrees and +180 degrees.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/center/indirect">Geocoder address service specification of the Map center.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/center/indirect/address">Address.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/center/indirect/region">Country code top-level domain within which to search. Optional.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/heading">The heading for aerial imagery in degrees measured clockwise from cardinal direction North. Headings are snapped to the nearest available angle for which imagery is available.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/maptypecontroloptions">The initial display options for the Map type control.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/maptypecontroloptions/position">Position id. Used to specify the position of the control on the map. The default position is TOP_RIGHT.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/maptypecontroloptions/style">Style id. Used to select what style of map type control to display.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/maptypecontroloptions/maptypeids">IDs of map types to show in the control.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/maptypecontroloptions/maptypeids/maptypeid">HYBRID 	This map type displays a transparent layer of major streets on satellite images.
ROADMAP 	This map type displays a normal street map.
SATELLITE 	This map type displays satellite images.
TERRAIN 	This map type displays maps with physical features such as terrain and vegetation.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/overviewmapcontroloptions">The display options for the Overview Map control.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/overviewmapcontroloptions/opened">Whether the control should display in opened mode or collapsed (minimized) mode. By default, the control is closed.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/pancontroloptions">The display options for the Pan control.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/pancontroloptions/position">Position id. Used to specify the position of the control on the map. The default position is TOP_LEFT.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/rotatecontroloptions">The display options for the Rotate control.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/rotatecontroloptions/position">Position id. Used to specify the position of the control on the map. The default position is TOP_LEFT.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/scalecontroloptions">Options for the rendering of the scale control.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/scalecontroloptions/position">Position id. Used to specify the position of the control on the map. The default position is BOTTOM_LEFT.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/streetview">A StreetViewPanorama to display when the Street View pegman is dropped on the map. If no panorama is specified, a default StreetViewPanorama will be displayed in the map's div when the pegman is dropped.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/streetview/oncloseclick">This event is fired when the close button is clicked.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/streetview/onpano_changed">This event is fired when the panorama's pano id changes. The pano may change as the user navigates through the panorama or the position is manually set. Note that not all position changes trigger a pano_changed.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/streetview/onposition_changed">This event is fired when the panorama's position changes. The position changes as the user navigates through the panorama or the position is set manually.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/streetview/onpov_changed">This event is fired when the panorama's point-of-view changes. The point of view changes as the pitch, zoom, or heading changes.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/streetview/onvisible_changed">This event is fired when the panorama's visibility changes. The visibility is changed when the Pegman id dragged onto the map, the close button is clicked, or setVisible() is called.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/streetview/streetviewoptions">Options defining the properties of a StreetViewPanorama.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/streetview/streetviewoptions/addresscontrol">The enabled/disabled state of the address control.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/streetview/streetviewoptions/disabledoubleclickzoom">Enables/disables zoom on double click. Disabled by default.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/streetview/streetviewoptions/enableclosebutton">If true, the close button is displayed. Disabled by default.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/streetview/streetviewoptions/linkscontrol">The enabled/disabled state of the links control.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/streetview/streetviewoptions/pancontrol">The enabled/disabled state of the pan control.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/streetview/streetviewoptions/pano">The panorama ID, which should be set when specifying a custom panorama.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/streetview/streetviewoptions/scrollwheel">If false, disables scrollwheel zooming in Street View. The scrollwheel is enabled by default.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/streetview/streetviewoptions/visible">If true, the Street View panorama is visible on load.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/streetview/streetviewoptions/zoomcontrol">The enabled/disabled state of the zoom control.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/streetview/streetviewoptions/addresscontroloptions">The display options for the address control.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/streetview/streetviewoptions/addresscontroloptions/position">Position id. This id is used to specify the position of the control on the map. The default position is TOP_LEFT.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/streetview/streetviewoptions/pancontroloptions">The display options for the pan control.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/streetview/streetviewoptions/pancontroloptions/position">Position id. Used to specify the position of the control on the map. The default position is TOP_LEFT.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/streetview/streetviewoptions/position">The position of the Street View panorama.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/streetview/streetviewoptions/position/direct">Direct lat/lng specification of the Street View position</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/streetview/streetviewoptions/position/direct/latitude">Latitude in degrees.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/streetview/streetviewoptions/position/direct/longitude">Longitude in degrees.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/streetview/streetviewoptions/position/direct/nowrap">If the noWrap flag is true, then the numbers will be used as passed, otherwise latitude will be clamped to lie between -90 degrees and +90 degrees, and longitude will be wrapped to lie between -180 degrees and +180 degrees.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/streetview/streetviewoptions/position/indirect">Indirect specification of the Street View position</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/streetview/streetviewoptions/position/indirect/address">Address.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/streetview/streetviewoptions/position/indirect/region">Country code top-level domain within which to search. Optional.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/streetview/streetviewoptions/pov">The camera orientation, specified as heading, pitch, and zoom, for the panorama.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/streetview/streetviewoptions/pov/heading">The camera heading in degrees relative to true north. True north is 0°, east is 90°, south is 180°, west is 270°.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/streetview/streetviewoptions/pov/pitch">The camera pitch in degrees, relative to the street view vehicle. Ranges from 90° (directly upwards) to -90° (directly downwards).</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/streetview/streetviewoptions/pov/zoom">	The zoom level. Fully zoomed-out is level 0, zooming in increases the zoom level.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/streetview/streetviewoptions/zoomcontroloptions">The display options for the zoom control.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/streetview/streetviewoptions/zoomcontroloptions/position">Position id. Used to specify the position of the control on the map. The default position is TOP_LEFT.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/streetview/streetviewoptions/zoomcontroloptions/style">Style id. Used to select what style of zoom control to display.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/streetviewcontroloptions">The initial display options for the Street View Pegman control.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/streetviewcontroloptions/position">Position id. Used to specify the position of the control on the map. The default position is embedded within the navigation (zoom and pan) controls. If this position is empty or the same as that specified in the zoomControlOptions or panControlOptions, the Street View control will be displayed as part of the navigation controls. Otherwise, it will be displayed separately.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/styles">Styles to apply to each of the default map types. Note that styles will apply only to the labels and geometry in Satellite/Hybrid and Terrain modes.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/styles/maptypestyle">The MapTypeStyle is a collection of selectors and stylers that define how the map should be styled. Selectors specify what map elements should be affected and stylers specify how those elements should be modified.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/styles/maptypestyle/elementtype">Selects the element type to which a styler should be applied. An element type distinguishes between the different representations of a feature. Optional; if elementType is not specified, the value is assumed to be 'all'.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/styles/maptypestyle/featuretype">Selects the feature, or group of features, to which a styler should be applied. Optional; if featureType is not specified, the value is assumed to be 'all'.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/styles/maptypestyle/stylers">The style rules to apply to the selectors. The rules are applied to the map's elements in the order they are listed in this collection.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/styles/maptypestyle/stylers/maptypestyler">A styler affects how a map's elements will be styled. Each MapTypeStyler should contain one and only one key. If more than one key is specified in a single MapTypeStyler, all but one will be ignored.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/styles/maptypestyle/stylers/maptypestyler/stylername">The property name of the styler (gamma, hue, invert_lightness, lightness, saturation, visibility)</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/styles/maptypestyle/stylers/maptypestyler/stylervalue">The value for the styler.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/tilt">The angle of incidence of the map as measured in degrees from the viewport plane to the map plane. The only currently supported values are 0, indicating no angle of incidence (no tilt), and 45, indicating a tilt of 45deg;. 45deg; imagery is only available for SATELLITE and HYBRID map types, within some locations, and at some zoom levels.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/zoomcontroloptions">The display options for the Zoom control.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/zoomcontroloptions/position">Position id. Used to specify the position of the control on the map. The default position is TOP_LEFT.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/options/zoomcontroloptions/style">Style id. Used to select what style of zoom control to display.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/markers">The collection of markers to display on the Map.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/markers/marker">A marker to display on the Map.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/markers/marker/draggable">If true, the marker can be dragged. Default value is false.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/markers/marker/clickable">If true, the marker receives mouse and touch events. Default value is true.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/markers/marker/cursor">Mouse cursor to show on hover</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/markers/marker/flat">If true, the marker shadow will not be displayed.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/markers/marker/optimized">Optimization renders many markers as a single static element. Optimized rendering is enabled by default.</entry>
	
	<entry path="/Maps/markers/marker/raiseondrag">If false, disables raising and lowering the marker on drag. This option is true by default.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/markers/marker/visible">If true, the marker is visible</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/markers/marker/onmarkerdragend">This event is fired when the user stops dragging the marker.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/markers/marker/onanimation_changed">This event is fired when the marker's animation property changes.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/markers/marker/onzindex_changed">This event is fired when the marker's zIndex property changes.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/markers/marker/position">Marker position. Required.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/markers/marker/position/direct">Direct lat/lng specification of the Marker position.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/markers/marker/position/direct/latitude">Latitude in degrees.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/markers/marker/position/direct/longitude">Longitude in degrees.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/markers/marker/position/indirect">Indirect specification of the Marker position.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/markers/marker/position/indirect/address">Address.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/markers/marker/position/indirect/region">Country code top-level domain within which to search. Optional.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/markers/marker/infowindow">An overlay that looks like a bubble and is connected to a marker.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/markers/marker/infowindow/disableautopan">Disable auto-pan on open. By default, the info window will pan the map so that it is fully visible when it opens.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/markers/marker/infowindow/maxwidth">Maximum width of the infowindow, regardless of content's width. This value is only considered if it is set before a call to open. </entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/markers/marker/infowindow/content">Content to display in the InfoWindow. This can be an HTML element, a plain-text string, or a string containing HTML. The InfoWindow will be sized according to the content. To set an explicit size for the content, set content to be a HTML element with that size.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/markers/marker/infowindow/pixeloffset">The offset, in pixels, of the tip of the info window from the point on the map at whose geographical coordinates the info window is anchored. If an InfoWindow is opened with an anchor, the pixelOffset will be calculated from the top-center of the anchor's bounds.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/markers/marker/infowindow/pixeloffset/width">The width along the x-axis, in pixels.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/markers/marker/infowindow/pixeloffset/height">The height along the y-axis, in pixels.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/markers/marker/infowindow/zindex">All InfoWindows are displayed on the map in order of their zIndex, with higher values displaying in front of InfoWindows with lower values. By default, InfoWinodws are displayed according to their latitude, with InfoWindows of lower latitudes appearing in front of InfoWindows at higher latitudes. InfoWindows are always displayed in front of markers.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/markers/marker/animation">Which animation to play when marker is added to a map.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/markers/marker/icon">Icon for the foreground</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/markers/marker/icon/url">The URL of the image or sprite sheet.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/markers/marker/icon/size">Two-dimensonal size, where width is the distance on the x-axis, and height is the distance on the y-axis.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/markers/marker/icon/size/height">The height along the y-axis, in pixels.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/markers/marker/icon/size/width">The width along the x-axis, in pixels.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/markers/marker/icon/origin">The position of the image within a sprite, if any. By default, the origin is located at the top left corner of the image (0, 0).</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/markers/marker/icon/origin/xcoord">The X coordinate</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/markers/marker/icon/origin/ycoord">The Y coordinate</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/markers/marker/icon/anchor">The position at which to anchor an image in correspondance to the location of the marker on the map. By default, the anchor is located along the center point of the bottom of the image.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/markers/marker/icon/anchor/xcoord">The X coordinate</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/markers/marker/icon/anchor/ycoord">The Y coordinate</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/markers/marker/icon/scaledsize">The size of the entire image after scaling, if any. Use this property to stretch/shrink an image or a sprite.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/markers/marker/icon/scaledsize/height">The height along the y-axis, in pixels.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/markers/marker/icon/scaledsize/width">The width along the x-axis, in pixels.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/markers/marker/shadow">Shadow image</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/markers/marker/shadow/url">The URL of the image or sprite sheet.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/markers/marker/shadow/size">The display size of the sprite or image. When using sprites, you must specify the sprite size. If the size is not provided, it will be set when the image loads.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/markers/marker/shadow/size/height">The height along the y-axis, in pixels.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/markers/marker/shadow/size/width">The width along the x-axis, in pixels.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/markers/marker/shadow/origin">The position of the image within a sprite, if any. By default, the origin is located at the top left corner of the image (0, 0).</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/markers/marker/shadow/origin/xcoord">The X coordinate</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/markers/marker/shadow/origin/ycoord">The Y coordinate</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/markers/marker/shadow/anchor">The position at which to anchor an image in correspondance to the location of the marker on the map. By default, the anchor is located along the center point of the bottom of the image.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/markers/marker/shadow/anchor/xcoord">The X coordinate</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/markers/marker/shadow/anchor/ycoord">The Y coordinate</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/markers/marker/shadow/scaledsize">The size of the entire image after scaling, if any. Use this property to stretch/shrink an image or a sprite.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/markers/marker/shadow/scaledsize/height">The height along the y-axis, in pixels.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/markers/marker/shadow/scaledsize/width">The width along the x-axis, in pixels.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/markers/marker/shape">Image map region definition used for drag/click.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/markers/marker/shape/type">Describes the shape's type and can be circle, poly or rect.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/markers/marker/shape/coords">The format of this attribute depends on the value of the type and follows the w3 AREA coords specification found at http://www.w3.org/TR/REC-html40/struct/objects.html#adef-coords.
The coords attribute is an array of integers that specify the pixel position of the shape relative to the top-left corner of the target image. The coordinates depend on the value of type as follows:
  - circle: coords is [x1,y1,r] where x1,y2 are the coordinates of the center of the circle, and r is the radius of the circle.
  - poly: coords is [x1,y1,x2,y2...xn,yn] where each x,y pair contains the coordinates of one vertex of the polygon.
  - rect: coords is [x1,y1,x2,y2] where x1,y1 are the coordinates of the upper-left corner of the rectangle and x2,y2 are the coordinates of the lower-right coordinates of the rectangle.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/markers/marker/shape/coords/shapecoord">A single coordinate in the collection of shape coordinates.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/markers/marker/shape/coords/shapecoord/coordvalue">Coordinate value.</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/markers/marker/title">Rollover text</entry>
	<entry path="/Maps/markers/marker/zindex">All markers are displayed on the map in order of their zIndex, with higher values displaying in front of markers with lower values. By default, markers are displayed according to their vertical position on screen, with lower markers appearing in front of markers further up the screen.</entry>
</doc>
